Technical University of British Columbia fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Office of the President records, 1986 - 2002; F-177-1; 8.65 m of textual records and other material; Dates of creation: Predominant dates of the series are 1995-2002. Physical description: Includes 46 photographs, 3 contact sheets, 14 videocassettes, 3 audio cassettes, 1 compact disk, and 2 artifa
  - Liaison records, 1993 - 2002; F-177-1-11; 1.87 m of textual records
    - Liaison - external committees and associations records, 1995 - 2001; F-177-1-11-3; 27 cm of textual records
      - Canadian Institutional Research and Planning Association (CIRPA), 1996 - 1999; F-177-1-11-3-8 (Archival box - standard 177-35)
      - CANARIE Inc., vol. 1, 1997 - 2000; F-177-1-11-3-9 (Archival box - standard 177-35)
      - CANARIE Inc., vol. 2, 1997 - 2000; F-177-1-11-3-10 (Archival box - standard 177-36)
      - C-Cnet [Canada-China High Speed Network], 1996 - 1997; F-177-1-11-3-11 (Archival box - standard 177-36)
      - Consulting Engineers of BC (CEBC), 1997 - 1999; F-177-1-11-3-12 (Archival box - standard 177-36)
      - Lower Mainland Education CEOs (G27 [and G28]), vol. 1, 1997 - 2000; F-177-1-11-3-13 (Archival box - standard 177-36)
      - Lower Mainland Education CEOs (G27 [and G28]), vol. 2, 1997 - 2000; F-177-1-11-3-14 (Archival box - standard 177-36)
      - Lower Mainland Education CEOs (G27 [and G28]), vol. 3, 1997 - 2000; F-177-1-11-3-15 (Archival box - standard 177-36)
      - Lower Mainland Education CEOs G-28 meeting, 02/27/2001, 2000 - 2001; F-177-1-11-3-16 (Archival box - standard 177-36)
      - PLNet [Provincial Learning Network], vol. 1, 1995 - 2001; F-177-1-11-3-17 (Archival box - standard 177-36)
      - PLNet [Provincial Learning Network], vol. 2, 1995 - 2001; F-177-1-11-3-18 (Archival box - standard 177-36)
      - PLNet [Provincial Learning Network], vol. 3, 1995 - 2001; F-177-1-11-3-19 (Archival box - standard 177-37)
    - Liaison - external organizations records, 1996 - 2001; F-177-1-11-4; 12 cm of textual records
      Sub-sub-series consists of records relating to TechBC's involvement with business and community organizations, locally and provincially. Records include correspondence; reports; minutes; newsletters, events notices, and promotional material; and membership information.
      - BC Advanced Systems Institute (ASI), 1999 - 2000; F-177-1-11-4-1 (Archival box - standard 177-37)
      - Business Council of BC, 1998 - 2000; F-177-1-11-4-2 (Archival box - standard 177-37)
      - Chamber of Commerce - BC, 1997 - 1999; F-177-1-11-4-3 (Archival box - standard 177-37)
      - Chamber of Commerce - Surrey - business excellence awards, 2001; F-177-1-11-4-5 (Archival box - standard 177-37)
      - Chamber of Commerce - Surrey - Spirit of Entrepreneurial Women dinner 2001, 1999 - 2001; F-177-1-11-4-6 (Archival box - standard 177-37)
      - Chamber of Commerce - Surrey - Cultural Diveristy Awards dinner 02/15/2001, 2000; F-177-1-11-4-7 (Archival box - standard 177-37)
      - Chamber of Commerce - Surrey, 1999 - 2001; F-177-1-11-4-8 (Archival box - standard 177-37)
      - Surrey Chamber Board meeting, 26 September 2000; F-177-1-11-4-9 (Archival box - standard 177-37)
      - Surrey Chamber - Board orientation and meeting, 08/22/2000, August 2000 - August 200; F-177-1-11-4-10 (Archival box - standard 177-37)
      - Contact North, 1998; F-177-1-11-4-11 (Archival box - standard 177-37)
      - Economic Development Association of BC (EDABC), 1999; F-177-1-11-4-12 (Archival box - standard 177-37)
      - Rotary clubs, 1996; F-177-1-11-4-13 (Archival box - standard 177-37)
      - School districts, 1997 - 1999; F-177-1-11-4-14 (Archival box - standard 177-37)
      - Science Council of BC, vol. 1, 1999; F-177-1-11-4-15 (Archival box - standard 177-37)
      - South Fraser Health Region, 1999 - 2000; F-177-1-11-4-16 (Archival box - standard 177-37)
      - Strong (David) proposal, 1999; F-177-1-11-4-17 (Archival box - standard 177-37)
      - Vancouver Board of Trade, vol. 1, 1999 - 2001; F-177-1-11-4-18 (Archival box - standard 177-37)
      - Vancouver Economic Development Commission, 1998; F-177-1-11-4-19 (Archival box - standard 177-37)
    - Liaison - government - federal records, 1998 - 2001; F-177-1-11-5; 5 cm of textual records
      Sub-sub-series consists of records relating to TechBC's correspondence and co-operation and liaison activities with the Federal Government, including government councils, commissions and committees. Records include correspondence, reports, booklets and press releases.
      The arrangement was provided by the archivist. Files are arranged alphabetically.
      - Advisory Committee on Online Learning (Admin), 2000 - 2001; F-177-1-11-5-1 (Archival box - standard 177-38)
      - Canadian Radio-television and Telecommunications Commission (CRTC), 2000; F-177-1-11-5-2 (Archival box - standard 177-38)
      - Council of Ministers of Education, Canada (CMEC), 1999 - 2000; F-177-1-11-5-3 (Archival box - standard 177-38)
      - Federal government - general, 1998 - 2001; F-177-1-11-5-4 (Archival box - standard 177-38)
      - The Governor General's Canadian Study Conference 2000, 1999; F-177-1-11-5-5 (Archival box - standard 177-38)
    - Liaison - government - municipal records, 1993 - 2001; F-177-1-11-6; 6 cm of textual records
      Sub-sub-series consists of records relating to TechBC's co-operation and liaison activities with various municipal governments, particularly the City of Surrey and the Greater Vancouver Regional District. Activities, events and topics documented include location proposals for the University and its eventual situation in Surrey, correspondence and meetings with the City of Surrey Council, meetings between TechBC and various community groups in Surrey, and TechBC's involvement in establishing community and economic development plans for the City of Surrey. Records include correspondence; minutes; reports; booklets, brochures and other promotional material; newspaper articles; and notes.
      - City of Surrey, vol. 1, 1995 - 2001; F-177-1-11-6-1 (Archival box - standard 177-38)
      - City of Surrey, vol. 2, 1995 - 2001; F-177-1-11-6-2 (Archival box - standard 177-38)
      - City of Surrey, vol. 3, 1995 - 2001; F-177-1-11-6-3 (Archival box - standard 177-38)
      - City of Surrey, vol. 1, 1993 - 1996; F-177-1-11-6-4 (Archival box - standard 177-38)
      - Greater Vancouver Regional District (GVRD), 1999; F-177-1-11-6-5 (Archival box - standard 177-38)
      - Municipal governments - various, 1996 - 1999; F-177-1-11-6-6 (Archival box - standard 177-38)
    - Liaison - government - provincial records, 1995 - 2001; F-177-1-11-7; 45 cm of textual records
      Sub-sub-series consists of records relating to TechBC's correspondence, co-operation and liaison activities, and general relations with the Provincial Government. Activities, events and topics documented include government funding and support for TechBC's development, including the designation of a permanent site; the President's participation in government committees, councils, summits and other meetings; correspondence and collaboration with MLAs, particularly Penny Priddy and Sue Hammell; liaison and co-operation with various Ministries, including the Ministry of Advanced Education, Training, and Technology, the Ministry of Labour, and the Ministry of Employment and Investment; and the government's support of post-secondary education and technology training in general. Records include correspondence; reports and briefing notes; minutes; booklets, newspaper articles, press releases, and newletters; presentations; and notes.
      - Provincial Government - general, vol. 1, 1995 - 2001; F-177-1-11-7-1 (Archival box - standard 177-38)
      - Provincial Government - general, vol. 2, 1995 - 2001; F-177-1-11-7-2 (Archival box - standard 177-38)
      - British Columbia Buildings Corporation, 1997 - 1998; F-177-1-11-7-3 (Archival box - standard 177-39)
      - BC Labour Force Development Board, vol. 1, 1995 - 1996; F-177-1-11-7-4 (Archival box - standard 177-39)
      - BC Labour Force Development Board, vol. 2, 1995 - 1996; F-177-1-11-7-5 (Archival box - standard 177-39)
      - Forest Renewal BC, 1996; F-177-1-11-7-6 (Archival box - standard 177-39)
      - Hansard reports, 1998; F-177-1-11-7-7 (Archival box - standard 177-39)
      - Hon. Penny Priddy, 1996 - 1998; F-177-1-11-7-8 (Archival box - standard 177-39)
      - Hon. Sue Hammell, 1997 - 1999; F-177-1-11-7-9 (Archival box - standard 177-39)
      - Industry Training and Apprenticeship Commission (ITAC), 1999; F-177-1-11-7-10 (Archival box - standard 177-39)
      - Information, Science and Technology Agency, Provincial Government, 1999 - 2000; F-177-1-11-7-11 (Archival box - standard 177-39)
      - Liberal MLAS, 2000; F-177-1-11-7-12 (Archival box - standard 177-39)
      - Meeting with Liberal Education Caucus, Parliament Buildings, Victoria, 6 December 2000; F-177-1-11-7-13 (Archival box - standard 177-39)
      - MAETT Review of TechBC, vol. 1, 2000; F-177-1-11-7-14 (Archival box - standard 177-39)
      - MAETT Review of TechBC, vol. 2, 2000; F-177-1-11-7-15 (Archival box - standard 177-39)
      - MAETT Review of TechBC, vol. 3, 2000; F-177-1-11-7-16 (Archival box - standard 177-40)
      - MAETT (TechBC specific), vol. 1, 1996 - 2001; F-177-1-11-7-17 (Archival box - standard 177-40)
      - MAETT (TechBC specific), vol. 2, 1996 - 2001; F-177-1-11-7-18 (Archival box - standard 177-40)
      - MAETT (TechBC specific), vol. 3, 1996 - 2001; F-177-1-11-7-19 (Archival box - standard 177-40)
      - MAETT - general, vol. 1, 1997 - 2001; F-177-1-11-7-20 (Archival box - standard 177-40)
      - MAETT - general, vol. 2, 1997 - 2001; F-177-1-11-7-21 (Archival box - standard 177-40)
      - MAETT - general, vol. 3, 1997 - 2001; F-177-1-11-7-22 (Archival box - standard 177-40)
      - MAETT - general, vol. 4, 1997 - 2001; F-177-1-11-7-23 (Archival box - standard 177-40)
      - MAETT - general, vol. 5, 1997 - 2001; F-177-1-11-7-24 (Archival box - standard 177-41)
      - MAETT - Minister's Forum on Universities, vol. 1, 1998 - 1999; F-177-1-11-7-25 (Archival box - standard 177-41)
      - MAETT - Minister's Forum on Universities, vol. 2, 1998 - 1999; F-177-1-11-7-26 (Archival box - standard 177-41)
      - MEI - Ministry of Employment and Investment, 1999 - 2000; F-177-1-11-7-27 (Archival box - standard 177-41)
      - Ministry of Finance and Corporate Relations (MFCR), vol. 1, 1999 - 2001; F-177-1-11-7-28 (Archival box - standard 177-41)
      - Ministry of Finance and Corporate Relations (MFCR), vol. 2, 1999 - 2001; F-177-1-11-7-29 (Archival box - standard 177-41)
      - Ministry of Finance and Corporate Relations (MFCR), vol. 3, 1999 - 2001; F-177-1-11-7-30 (Archival box - standard 177-41)
      - Ministry of Finance and Corporate Relations (MFCR), vol. 4, 1999 - 2001; F-177-1-11-7-31 (Archival box - standard 177-41)
      - Ministry of Labour, 2000; F-177-1-11-7-32 (Archival box - standard 177-42)
      - News releases, vol. 1, 1997 - 1999; F-177-1-11-7-33 (Archival box - standard 177-42)
      - Premier's Council on Technology, 2001; F-177-1-11-7-34 (Archival box - standard 177-42)
      - Public Sector Employers' Council, 1995 - 2000; F-177-1-11-7-35 (Archival box - standard 177-42)
      - [Minister's] Summit on Software Industry Skills Shortages, 1996 - 1998; F-177-1-11-7-36 (Archival box - standard 177-42)
      - E-Learning in Canada: Skills and Learning Policy Directorate Strategic Policy, 5 October 2001; F-177-1-11-7-37 (Archival box - standard 177-42)
    - Liaison - post-secondary education records, 1995 - 1999; F-177-1-11-8; 1 cm of textual records
      Sub-sub-series consists of records relating to TechBC's liaison activities with other post-secondary institutions, and includes material regarding British Columbia universities, university-colleges, colleges, and institutes in general, as well as records relating to TechBC's relations with Canadian universities outside of British Columbia. Records include correspondence, reports, minutes, and newsletters.
      - Post-secondary education - general, 1995 - 1999; F-177-1-11-8-1 (Archival box - standard 177-42)
  - President's Office files, 1995 - 2002; F-177-1-12; 27 cm of textual records
    Sub-series consists of records relating to the position and activities of the President of TechBC. Activities, events and topics documented include Presidential recruiting and compensation; speeches made by the President, President's Annual Reports; activities of the President's Executive Advisory Committee (PEAC); and Vice-Presidential duties, objectives and activities. Records include correspondence; reports, papers, speeches and presentations; minutes, agendas and supporting documents; annual reports; and contracts.
    Technical University of British Columbia. President's Executive Advisory Committee
    - BSS [Bernie S. Sheehan] - compensation (personal), vol. 1, 1996 - 2001; F-177-1-12-0-1 (Archival box - standard 177-42)
    - BSS [Bernie S. Sheehan] - compensation (personal), vol. 2, 1996 - 2001; F-177-1-12-0-2 (Archival box - standard 177-42)
    - BSS [Bernie S. Sheehan] - compensation (personal) [photographs], 1996 - 2001; F-177-1-12-0-3 (Archival box - small 177-68)
      Textual records; Photographic materials
    - BSS [Bernie S. Sheehan] - notes to Jean Watters, 2001; F-177-1-12-0-4 (Archival box - standard 177-42)
    - CEO Regional Task Force, 1995 - 1997; F-177-1-12-0-5 (Archival box - standard 177-42)
    - Correspondence (miscellaneous), vol. 1, 1999 - 2000; F-177-1-12-0-6 (Archival box - standard 177-42)
    - New universities planning meeting - San Francisco, 1999; F-177-1-12-0-7 (Archival box - standard 177-42)
    - PEAC [President's Executive Advisory Council] agendas [and related documents], vol. 1, 12 March 1999 - 29 March 1999; F-177-1-12-0-8 (Archival box - standard 177-42)
    - PEAC [President's Executive Advisory Council] agendas [and related documents], vol. 2, 19 February 1999 - 2 March 1999; F-177-1-12-0-9 (Archival box - standard 177-43)
    - PEAC [President's Executive Advisory Council] agendas [and related documents], vol. 3, 7 December 1998 - 9 February 1999; F-177-1-12-0-10 (Archival box - standard 177-43)
    - PEAC [President's Executive Advisory Council] agendas [and related documents], vol. 4, 14 September 1998 - 9 November 1998; F-177-1-12-0-11 (Archival box - standard 177-43)
    - PEAC [President's Executive Advisory Council] agendas [and related documents], vol. 5, 4 June 1998 - 31 August 1998; F-177-1-12-0-12 (Archival box - standard 177-43)
    - PEAC [President's Executive Advisory Council] agendas [and related documents], vol. 6, 1 December 1997 - 20 April 1998; F-177-1-12-0-13 (Archival box - standard 177-43)
    - PEAC [President's Executive Advisory Council] strategic planning meeting, May 10, 1999, 1998 - 1999; F-177-1-12-0-14 (Archival box - standard 177-43)
    - Presidential search 2000, vol. 1, 2000 - 2001; F-177-1-12-0-15 (Archival box - standard 177-43)
    - Presidential search 2000, vol. 2, 2000 - 2001; F-177-1-12-0-16 (Archival box - standard 177-43)
    - Presidential search 2000, vol. 3, 2000 - 2001; F-177-1-12-0-17 (Archival box - standard 177-43)
    - President's annual report, vol. 1, 1998 - 2000; F-177-1-12-0-18 (Archival box - standard 177-44)
    - President's annual report, vol. 2, 1998 - 2000; F-177-1-12-0-19 (Archival box - standard 177-44)
    - Speeches, 1996 - 1999; F-177-1-12-0-20 (Archival box - standard 177-44)
    - Vice President, Academic, 1997 - 2001; F-177-1-12-0-21 (Archival box - standard 177-44)
    - Vice President, Research and External Affairs, 1997 - 2002; F-177-1-12-0-22 (Archival box - standard 177-44)
    - Vice presidents' job descriptions, 1997 - 1999; F-177-1-12-0-23 (Archival box - standard 177-44)
  - Systems support records, 1995 - 2001; F-177-1-13; 13 cm of textual records
    Sub-series consists of records relating to the development of computer, internet, telecommunications, information technology, and administrative systems and networks at TechBC. Includes records documenting the activities of the TechBC Systems Planning and Development Advisory Committee (SPDAC) and University participation in the BCNet Society. Records include correspondence; reports, proposals, briefs, and presentations; minutes, agendas, and supporting papers; newspaper articles; and reference material.
    Technical University of British Columbia. Systems Planning and Development Advisory Committee
    - BCnet, vol. 1, 1995 - 2001; F-177-1-13-0-1 (Archival box - standard 177-44)
    - BCnet, vol. 2, 1995 - 2001; F-177-1-13-0-2 (Archival box - standard 177-44)
    - Computer systems, 1996 - 2000; F-177-1-13-0-3 (Archival box - standard 177-44)
    - Information technology, vol. 1, 1996 - 2000; F-177-1-13-0-4 (Archival box - standard 177-44)
    - Information technology, vol. 2, 1996 - 2000; F-177-1-13-0-5 (Archival box - standard 177-44)
    - Internet II, 1995 - 1997; F-177-1-13-0-6 (Archival box - standard 177-45)
    - Records management project, 1999 - 2000; F-177-1-13-0-7 (Archival box - standard 177-45)
    - Software information, 1997; F-177-1-13-0-8 (Archival box - standard 177-45)
    - Systems Planning and Development Advisory Committee (SPDAC), vol. 1, 1998 - 2001; F-177-1-13-0-9 (Archival box - standard 177-45)
    - Systems Planning and Development Advisory Committee (SPDAC), vol. 2, 1998 - 2001; F-177-1-13-0-10 (Archival box - standard 177-45)
    - Systems Planning and Development Advisory Committee (SPDAC), vol. 3, 1998 - 2001; F-177-1-13-0-11 (Archival box - standard 177-45)
    - Systems Planning and Development Advisory Committee (SPDAC): business case and recommendation for purchase, electronic records management software, 2000; F-177-1-13-0-12 (Archival box - standard 177-45)
    - Telecommunications systems, 1995; F-177-1-13-0-13 (Archival box - standard 177-45)
  - Institutional research files, 1995 - 1997; F-177-1-14; 3 cm of textual records
    Sub-series consists of reference files maintained by the Office of the President relating to academic planning, tenure, and legal issues. Records include correspondence, photocopied articles, and notes.
    - I.R. - academic planning - general, 1996 - 1997; F-177-1-14-0-1 (Archival box - standard 177-45)
    - I.R. - administration - legal issues, 1995 - 1997; F-177-1-14-0-2 (Archival box - standard 177-45)
    - I.R. - personnel - tenure, 1997; F-177-1-14-0-3 (Archival box - standard 177-45)
  - Contract researcher files, 1993 - 1998; F-177-1-15; 34 cm of textual records
    Sub-series consists of records compiled and created by a contract researcher hired by the Office of the President. Includes files of documents relating to the Fraser Valley University Society and TechBC, compiled by the researcher to write a history of TechBC and to create an Archives for the University. Records also include working papers and drafts of the "History of the Technical University of British Columbia" and an inventory of Fraser Valley University Society records in TechBC's custody. The sub-series also includes records relating to research performed concerning applied science and research programs; proposed partnerships with corporations, industry, BCIT and Simon Fraser University; and other reports relating to the development of the University. Records include reports; correspondence; working papers and notes; minutes; promotional material, brochures, newspaper articles and press releases; and legislation. Records include both photocopies and originals.
    Fraser Valley University Society
    - 1907-8 - debates on technical education, Nova Scotia, 1997; F-177-1-15-0-1 (Archival box - standard 177-45)
    - 1989 and previous, 1997; F-177-1-15-0-2 (Archival box - standard 177-45)
    - 1990, vol. 1, 1997; F-177-1-15-0-3 (Archival box - standard 177-45)
    - 1990, vol. 2, 1997; F-177-1-15-0-4 (Archival box - standard 177-46)
    - 1991, vol. 1, 1997; F-177-1-15-0-5 (Archival box - standard 177-46)
    - 1991, vol. 2, 1997; F-177-1-15-0-6 (Archival box - standard 177-46)
    - 1992, vol. 1, 1997; F-177-1-15-0-7 (Archival box - standard 177-46)
    - 1992, vol. 2, 1997; F-177-1-15-0-8 (Archival box - standard 177-46)
    - 1993, vol. 1, 1997; F-177-1-15-0-9 (Archival box - standard 177-46)
    - 1993, vol. 2, 1997; F-177-1-15-0-10 (Archival box - standard 177-46)
    - 1994, vol. 1, 1997; F-177-1-15-0-11 (Archival box - standard 177-46)
    - 1994, vol. 2, 1997; F-177-1-15-0-12 (Archival box - standard 177-46)
    - 1995, vol. 1, 1997 - 1995; F-177-1-15-0-13 (Archival box - standard 177-46)
    - 1995, vol. 2, 1997; F-177-1-15-0-14 (Archival box - standard 177-46)
    - 1997, F-177-1-15-0-15 (Archival box - standard 177-46)
    - Internal Planning Report 97-021: History of the Technical University of BC, 1997; F-177-1-15-0-16 (Archival box - standard 177-47)
    - Historical documents [working papers], vol. 1, 1997; F-177-1-15-0-17 (Archival box - standard 177-47)
    - Historical documents [working papers], vol. 2, 1997; F-177-1-15-0-18 (Archival box - standard 177-47)
    - Historical documents [working papers], vol. 3, 1997; F-177-1-15-0-19 (Archival box - standard 177-47)
    - Historical documents [working papers], vol. 4, 1997; F-177-1-15-0-20 (Archival box - standard 177-47)
    - Contract work, 1997; F-177-1-15-0-21 (Archival box - standard 177-47)
    - Applied research program initiative, 1995 - 1997; F-177-1-15-0-22 (Archival box - standard 177-47)
    - Internal report: applied and pure research [working file], 1996 - 1997; F-177-1-15-0-23 (Archival box - standard 177-47)
    - [Visits to other universities], 1996 - 1997; F-177-1-15-0-24 (Archival box - standard 177-47)
    - Alliance, vol. 1, 1997; F-177-1-15-0-25 (Archival box - standard 177-47)
    - Bill 30 and debates in legislature, 1997; F-177-1-15-0-26 (Archival box - standard 177-47)
    - Internal Planning Report 96-004: Demographic, Educational and Occupational Profiles of 1988 Graduates…, vol. 1, October 1996; F-177-1-15-0-27 (Archival box - standard 177-47)
    - Internal Planning Report 96-005: Local Industry Needs Analysis, vol. 1, November 1996; F-177-1-15-0-28 (Archival box - standard 177-47)
    - Internal Planning Report 96-006: Technical University of BC Annual Report, 1996, vol. 1, F-177-1-15-0-29 (Archival box - standard 177-48)
    - Internal Planning Report 96-007: Connected in a Network: TechBC - its Students, the Labour Market, Industry and Society, vol. 1, 28 November 1996; F-177-1-15-0-30 (Archival box - standard 177-48)
    - Report: The Need for a University in the Fraser Valley: A Case Study for Educators, January 1998; F-177-1-15-0-31 (Archival box - standard 177-48)
    - Report of the Fraser Valley Committee on Post-Secondary Education, Phase I, vol. 1, June 1993; F-177-1-15-0-32 (Archival box - standard 177-48)
    - Inventories - Fraser Valley University Society, 1997; F-177-1-15-0-33 (Archival box - standard 177-48)
    - UBC/SFU/UVIC start-up difficulties, vol. 1, 1997; F-177-1-15-0-34 (Archival box - standard 177-48)
    - UBC/SFU/UVIC start-up difficulties, vol. 2, 1997; F-177-1-15-0-35 (Archival box - standard 177-48)
  - President's historical files, 1993 - 2001; F-177-1-16; 92 cm of textual records 42 photographs 3 contact sheets 1 compact disk